

# **JORDAN ALEXIS**

#### **Junior Programmer and Designer**

Brooklyn, NY 11212 alexisjordan842@gmail.com 16466258972

As a programmer, I can make websites, video games, and computer networks from scratch.

As a designer, it gave me many years of learning about how the field of my occupation works. I have used many applications at my disposal to create graphic arts like Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, XD, and Illustrator.

Using different programming languages, I publish websites on GitHub, Wix, WordPress, and use programs like Unity, Game Maker, Maya, Unreal Engine to make and produce games.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Spring Intern**

**WBAI Radio** - Brooklyn, NY January 2019 to May 2019

- · Assisted in Sorting and Mailing out prizes for their WBAI Buddies.
- · Managed their Social Media Using Hootsuite
- Assigned managing some Customer Service tasks.
- Assisted in their event calendar by using Photoshop to make the pictures for each articlepresentable.
- · Assisted in entering important personal data for their WBAI Buddies.

## **Multimedia Internship**

**SYEP, The Challenge Publisher Group** - Brooklyn, NY July 2018 to August 2018

Assisted in creating a modernized version of a newspaper called "The New American" by making it in Adobe InDesign from scratch.

- Used Photoshop to make images given to me more presentable.
- Distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York.

## **Multimedia Developer Internship**

SYEP, St. John's Recreation Center - Brooklyn, NY

July 2017 to August 2017

- Learned about Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign effectively.
- Learned how to record audio using GarageBand and using audio to create a 3-5-minute video using Windows Media Player.

# **Day Care Worker**

SYEP, Charles Churn Christian Academy - Brooklyn, NY

July 2014 to August 2014

- Assisted making sure the children (5-10) went to their destinations safely.
- · Assisted in making activities, organized the work and camp environment.
- Carried equipment to wherever they needed to be.

#### SKILL SET

#### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- Intermediate Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, and XD.
- · Understanding and Translating computer data, proficiency in cloud computing, IT, basic audio production.
- Intermediate knowledge of creating and designing websites.
- Have intermediate skills in Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.
- · Have basic knowledge using Social Media.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor's in Science, Major: Multimedia Computing and Computer Systems

Brooklyn College - Brooklyn, NY

August 2019 to Present

#### Associate in Science, Major: Multimedia Programming and Design

Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) - Manhattan, NY

August 2017 to May 2019

## **Credits towards Networking Technology Degree in Communications**

Technical Career Institute (TCI) - Manhattan, NY

January 2017 to May 2017

## **Credits in Credits towards Computer Information Systems**

Bramson Ort College - Queens, NY

October 2014 to January 2017

#### LINKS

http://jordan721.github.io/Jordan\_Alexis

http://www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-alexis-799214175

https://www.facebook.com/jordan.alexis.l

https://www.instagram.com/jordan.alexis.l/